<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><root xml:space="preserve">
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Acceleration.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<brief errors="2">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="37">
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="18">
			line= 2 length= 232
			line= 3 length= 248
			line= 4 length= 218
			line= 5 length= 218
			line= 6 length= 246
			line= 7 length= 230
			line= 8 length= 141
			line= 22 length= 146
			line= 23 length= 130
			line= 24 length= 208
			line= 25 length= 218
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 82
			line= 30 length= 83
			line= 32 length= 83
			line= 35 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 83
			line= 75 length= 81
		</linelength>
		<inclusion-guards errors="2">
			Invalid ifndef found for Inclusion Guard!
		</inclusion-guards>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/ADT_Base.hpp">
		<Indentation errors="120">
			Indentation on line 41 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 44 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'v'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'v'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 99 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 101 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'v'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 105 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 106 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 107 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 108 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 109 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 110 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 111 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 114 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 115 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 116 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 117 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 118 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 119 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 120 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'v'
			Indentation on line 121 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 124 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 125 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 126 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 127 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 128 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 129 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 130 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 131 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 133 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 136 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 137 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 138 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 139 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 140 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 141 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 142 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 143 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'v'
			Indentation on line 145 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 148 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 149 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 150 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 151 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 152 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 153 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 154 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 155 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 157 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 160 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 161 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 162 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 163 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 164 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 165 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 166 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 167 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 168 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 172 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 173 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 174 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 175 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 176 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 177 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 178 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 181 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 182 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 183 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 184 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 185 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 186 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 187 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 190 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 192 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="10">
			line= 13 length= 146
			line= 14 length= 130
			line= 15 length= 208
			line= 16 length= 218
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 20 length= 82
			line= 21 length= 83
			line= 23 length= 83
			line= 26 length= 81
			line= 27 length= 83
		</linelength>
		<inclusion-guards errors="2">
			Invalid ifndef found for Inclusion Guard!
		</inclusion-guards>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Angle.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<brief errors="2">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="2">
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="23">
			line= 2 length= 232
			line= 3 length= 248
			line= 4 length= 216
			line= 5 length= 216
			line= 6 length= 246
			line= 7 length= 230
			line= 22 length= 146
			line= 23 length= 130
			line= 24 length= 208
			line= 25 length= 218
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 82
			line= 30 length= 83
			line= 32 length= 83
			line= 35 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 83
			line= 66 length= 87
			line= 72 length= 85
			line= 75 length= 84
			line= 77 length= 83
			line= 101 length= 85
			line= 104 length= 84
			line= 131 length= 83
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Attitude.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 36 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="5">
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 143 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 145 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="9">
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 20 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 81
			line= 31 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 81
			line= 103 length= 81
			line= 111 length= 81
			line= 118 length= 81
			line= 142 length= 81
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Box.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<brief errors="2">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="81">
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 101 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 103 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 104 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 105 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 106 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 107 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 108 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 110 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 111 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 112 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 113 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 115 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 116 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 117 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 118 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 119 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 121 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 122 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 123 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 124 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 125 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 126 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 128 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 129 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 130 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 131 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 132 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 133 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 135 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 136 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 137 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 138 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 139 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 141 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="18">
			line= 2 length= 232
			line= 3 length= 248
			line= 4 length= 218
			line= 5 length= 218
			line= 6 length= 246
			line= 7 length= 230
			line= 8 length= 141
			line= 22 length= 146
			line= 23 length= 130
			line= 24 length= 208
			line= 25 length= 218
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 82
			line= 30 length= 83
			line= 32 length= 83
			line= 35 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 83
			line= 48 length= 81
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Coordinate.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 34 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="105">
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 99 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 103 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 104 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 105 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 106 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 108 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 109 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 110 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 111 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 112 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 114 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 115 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 116 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 117 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 118 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 120 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 121 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 123 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 124 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 125 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 126 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 127 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 128 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 129 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 130 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 131 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 132 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 133 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 134 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 136 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 137 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 138 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 139 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 140 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 141 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 142 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 143 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 144 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 145 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 146 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 147 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 148 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 149 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 150 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 151 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 153 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 154 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 155 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 156 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 158 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 159 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 160 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 161 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 163 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 164 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 165 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 166 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 167 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 169 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="24">
			line= 22 length= 83
			line= 26 length= 82
			line= 27 length= 83
			line= 28 length= 84
			line= 30 length= 84
			line= 33 length= 82
			line= 34 length= 84
			line= 57 length= 84
			line= 66 length= 81
			line= 77 length= 83
			line= 102 length= 82
			line= 108 length= 82
			line= 114 length= 87
			line= 126 length= 85
			line= 129 length= 89
			line= 136 length= 86
			line= 140 length= 83
			line= 148 length= 92
			line= 153 length= 85
			line= 155 length= 86
			line= 158 length= 85
			line= 160 length= 86
			line= 163 length= 85
			line= 165 length= 86
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Duration.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 35 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="3">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
				Version on line: 3
				Version on line: 40
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="9">
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 135 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 137 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="5">
			line= 18 length= 81
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 30 length= 81
			line= 35 length= 81
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Force.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 31 through 35 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="51">
			Indentation on line 44 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'F'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'F'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'F'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="10">
			line= 15 length= 146
			line= 16 length= 130
			line= 17 length= 208
			line= 18 length= 218
			line= 21 length= 81
			line= 22 length= 82
			line= 23 length= 83
			line= 25 length= 83
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 83
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Length.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 36 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="3">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
				Version on line: 4
				Version on line: 40
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="11">
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 126 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 128 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="5">
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 20 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 81
			line= 31 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 81
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Mass.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 89 through 89 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="43">
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="10">
			line= 15 length= 146
			line= 16 length= 130
			line= 17 length= 208
			line= 18 length= 218
			line= 21 length= 81
			line= 22 length= 82
			line= 23 length= 83
			line= 25 length= 83
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 83
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Moment.hpp">
		<Indentation errors="81">
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'v'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 99 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 101 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 103 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'D'
			Indentation on line 105 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 106 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 107 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 108 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 109 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 110 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 112 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 113 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 114 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 115 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 116 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 117 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 118 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 120 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 121 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 122 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 123 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 124 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 126 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 127 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 128 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 129 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 130 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 131 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 132 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 134 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 135 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 136 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 137 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 138 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 139 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 140 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 141 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 142 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 144 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="10">
			line= 15 length= 146
			line= 16 length= 130
			line= 17 length= 208
			line= 18 length= 218
			line= 21 length= 81
			line= 22 length= 82
			line= 23 length= 83
			line= 25 length= 83
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 83
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Rotation.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 36 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="5">
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 133 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 135 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="5">
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 20 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 81
			line= 31 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 81
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Speed.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 30 through 30 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="65">
			Indentation on line 39 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 41 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 44 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'S'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'S'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 101 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 103 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 104 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 105 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 106 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 107 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 108 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 110 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'S'
			Indentation on line 112 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="12">
			line= 15 length= 146
			line= 16 length= 130
			line= 17 length= 208
			line= 18 length= 218
			line= 21 length= 81
			line= 22 length= 82
			line= 23 length= 83
			line= 25 length= 83
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 83
			line= 94 length= 82
			line= 102 length= 82
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/include/Translation.hpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 36 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="23">
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 113 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 124 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 135 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 146 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 169 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 190 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 211 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 249 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 251 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 253 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '#'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="8">
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 20 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 81
			line= 31 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 81
			line= 114 length= 81
			line= 125 length= 81
			line= 164 length= 81
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Acceleration.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<brief errors="2">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="48">
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'w'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 99 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 103 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 105 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="23">
			line= 2 length= 232
			line= 3 length= 248
			line= 4 length= 218
			line= 5 length= 218
			line= 6 length= 246
			line= 7 length= 230
			line= 8 length= 141
			line= 22 length= 146
			line= 23 length= 130
			line= 24 length= 208
			line= 25 length= 218
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 82
			line= 30 length= 83
			line= 32 length= 83
			line= 35 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 83
			line= 59 length= 81
			line= 65 length= 89
			line= 68 length= 85
			line= 69 length= 92
			line= 84 length= 84
			line= 94 length= 90
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Angle.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<brief errors="2">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<linelength errors="16">
			line= 2 length= 232
			line= 3 length= 248
			line= 4 length= 216
			line= 5 length= 216
			line= 6 length= 246
			line= 7 length= 230
			line= 22 length= 146
			line= 23 length= 130
			line= 24 length= 208
			line= 25 length= 218
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 82
			line= 30 length= 83
			line= 32 length= 83
			line= 35 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 83
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Attitude.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 36 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="49">
			Indentation on line 40 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 41 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 99 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 101 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 104 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 105 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 106 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 107 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 108 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 111 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 112 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="5">
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 20 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 81
			line= 31 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 81
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Box.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<brief errors="4">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 1 does not contain a brief description.
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 79 through 80 does not contain a brief description.
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 111 through 112 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="131">
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 44 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ')'
			Indentation on line 99 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 101 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 103 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 104 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 107 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 110 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 111 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 112 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 113 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 114 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 115 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 117 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 120 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 121 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 122 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 123 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 124 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 125 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 126 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 127 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 128 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 129 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 132 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 135 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 136 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 139 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 140 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 143 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 144 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 145 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 147 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '('
			Indentation on line 148 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'n'
			Indentation on line 151 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '('
			Indentation on line 152 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'n'
			Indentation on line 154 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '('
			Indentation on line 155 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'n'
			Indentation on line 157 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '('
			Indentation on line 158 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'n'
			Indentation on line 160 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '('
			Indentation on line 161 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'n'
			Indentation on line 163 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '('
			Indentation on line 164 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'n'
			Indentation on line 166 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 169 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 170 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 171 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 172 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 173 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 174 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 175 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 176 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 178 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 179 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 180 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 184 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 185 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 186 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 187 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 188 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 189 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 192 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'B'
			Indentation on line 193 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 194 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 195 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 198 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 199 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 200 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 203 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 204 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 205 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 207 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 209 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 210 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 211 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '"'
			Indentation on line 213 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 214 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 215 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 216 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 219 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 220 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 222 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 223 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 225 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 226 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 227 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '"'
			Indentation on line 230 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 231 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 232 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="18">
			line= 2 length= 232
			line= 3 length= 248
			line= 4 length= 218
			line= 5 length= 218
			line= 6 length= 246
			line= 7 length= 230
			line= 8 length= 141
			line= 22 length= 146
			line= 23 length= 130
			line= 24 length= 208
			line= 25 length= 218
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 82
			line= 30 length= 83
			line= 32 length= 83
			line= 35 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 83
			line= 226 length= 82
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Coordinate.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 35 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="73">
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'o'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'C'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'o'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '"'
			Indentation on line 99 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'p'
			Indentation on line 101 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 103 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 104 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 107 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 108 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 109 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 110 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 112 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 113 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 114 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'a'
			Indentation on line 115 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 116 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 117 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 118 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 119 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 121 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 122 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 123 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 124 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 125 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 127 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 128 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 129 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '"'
			Indentation on line 132 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 133 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 134 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 136 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 139 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 140 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 143 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 144 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 147 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 148 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="9">
			line= 15 length= 85
			line= 24 length= 85
			line= 27 length= 82
			line= 28 length= 83
			line= 29 length= 84
			line= 31 length= 84
			line= 34 length= 82
			line= 35 length= 84
			line= 129 length= 91
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Duration.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 35 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="25">
			Indentation on line 41 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'D'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'D'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '"'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '"'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="6">
			line= 18 length= 81
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 30 length= 81
			line= 35 length= 81
			line= 69 length= 85
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Force.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="52">
			Indentation on line 34 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 35 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'F'
			Indentation on line 38 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'F'
			Indentation on line 40 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 41 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'o'
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'w'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'k'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'F'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'S'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="10">
			line= 15 length= 146
			line= 16 length= 130
			line= 17 length= 208
			line= 18 length= 218
			line= 21 length= 81
			line= 22 length= 82
			line= 23 length= 83
			line= 25 length= 83
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 83
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Length.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 36 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="44">
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'w'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="11">
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 20 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 81
			line= 31 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 81
			line= 63 length= 101
			line= 68 length= 89
			line= 71 length= 85
			line= 72 length= 92
			line= 87 length= 86
			line= 97 length= 122
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Mass.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="35">
			Indentation on line 35 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 36 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 37 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 39 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'o'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 58 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'w'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'e'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'k'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="10">
			line= 15 length= 146
			line= 16 length= 130
			line= 17 length= 208
			line= 18 length= 218
			line= 21 length= 81
			line= 22 length= 82
			line= 23 length= 83
			line= 25 length= 83
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 83
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Moment.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="58">
			Indentation on line 34 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 36 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 37 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 38 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 44 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 54 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'D'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'a'
			Indentation on line 78 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 85 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 86 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'M'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 93 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 101 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'o'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 103 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 106 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 107 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 108 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 109 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 110 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 112 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 113 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="10">
			line= 15 length= 146
			line= 16 length= 130
			line= 17 length= 208
			line= 18 length= 218
			line= 21 length= 81
			line= 22 length= 82
			line= 23 length= 83
			line= 25 length= 83
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 83
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Rotation.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 36 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="43">
			Indentation on line 40 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 41 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 42 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 47 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 48 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 53 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'A'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 94 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'R'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 101 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 102 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="5">
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 20 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 81
			line= 31 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 81
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Speed.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<author errors="1">
				No authors are specified in the file.
			</author>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 30 through 30 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
			<version errors="1">
				A file should have 1 version specified; no more no less.
			</version>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="34">
			Indentation on line 34 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'S'
			Indentation on line 36 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 37 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'S'
			Indentation on line 38 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 39 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 41 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 44 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 46 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 50 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'o'
			Indentation on line 57 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 61 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 62 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '/'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 70 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 71 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'f'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 77 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'k'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="10">
			line= 15 length= 146
			line= 16 length= 130
			line= 17 length= 208
			line= 18 length= 218
			line= 21 length= 81
			line= 22 length= 82
			line= 23 length= 83
			line= 25 length= 83
			line= 28 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 83
		</linelength>
	</file>
	<file file_name="E:\Development\HBO\Year2\BlokC\ThemaOpdracht7-8\adt\source/src/Translation.cpp">
		<doxygen>
			<brief errors="1">
				Doxygen comment on line(s) 1 through 36 does not contain a brief description.
			</brief>
		</doxygen>
		<Indentation errors="118">
			Indentation on line 39 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 43 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 45 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 49 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '{'
			Indentation on line 51 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 52 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 55 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 56 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 59 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 60 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 63 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 64 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 65 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 66 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 67 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 68 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 69 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 72 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 73 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 74 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 75 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 76 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 79 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 80 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 81 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 82 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 83 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 84 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 87 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 88 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 89 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 90 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 91 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 92 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 95 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 96 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 97 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 98 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 99 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 100 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 103 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 104 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 105 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 106 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 107 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 108 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 110 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 111 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 112 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 113 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 114 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 116 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 117 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 118 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 119 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 122 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 123 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 124 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 125 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 126 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'd'
			Indentation on line 127 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 128 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 129 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 130 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 132 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 134 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 135 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 136 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 137 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 138 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 139 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 141 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 142 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'T'
			Indentation on line 143 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 144 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 145 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 146 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 148 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 149 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 150 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 152 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 153 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'b'
			Indentation on line 154 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 156 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '	'
			Indentation on line 157 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 158 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 159 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 162 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 163 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 's'
			Indentation on line 164 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 165 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 166 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 167 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '"'
			Indentation on line 168 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 170 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 171 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 172 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 173 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 176 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 178 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'a'
			Indentation on line 179 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'L'
			Indentation on line 180 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'c'
			Indentation on line 181 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'l'
			Indentation on line 182 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 183 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 185 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 186 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 187 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'x'
			Indentation on line 188 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'y'
			Indentation on line 189 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'z'
			Indentation on line 191 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'i'
			Indentation on line 192 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 't'
			Indentation on line 193 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character '"'
			Indentation on line 194 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character ';'
			Indentation on line 196 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 197 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 198 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
			Indentation on line 199 is not according to the standard. Encountered unexpected character 'r'
		</Indentation>
		<linelength errors="8">
			line= 19 length= 81
			line= 20 length= 81
			line= 29 length= 81
			line= 31 length= 81
			line= 36 length= 81
			line= 68 length= 84
			line= 158 length= 84
			line= 193 length= 84
		</linelength>
	</file>
</root>
